export default data = [
    {
        question: "How many All Star Appearances does Kobe Bryant have?",
        options: ["16","17","18","19"],
        correct_option: "18"
    },
    {
        question: "What city won the first NBA Championship?",
        options: ["Chicago","Los Angeles","Baltimore", "Philadelphia"],
        correct_option: "Philadelphia"
    },
    {
        question: "Who was the hardest player to guard for Kobe Bryant?",
        options: ["Tracy McGrady","Kevin Durant","Allen Iverson","Michael Jordan"],
        correct_option: "Kevin Durant"
    },
    {
        question: "Who was Michael Jordan toughest defender?",
        options: ["Gary Payton","Joe Dumars","Dennis Rodman","Isaiah Thomas"],
        correct_option: "Joe Dumars"
    },
    {
        question: "What year was the Milwaukee Bucks 1st Championship?",
        options: ["1970","1971","1972","1974"],
        correct_option: "1972"
    },
    {
        question: "Who scored the most career points in NBA History?",
        options: ["Lebron James","Kobe Bryant","Michael Jordan","Kareem Abdul-Jabbar"],
        correct_option: "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar"
    },
    {
        question: "What year did Giannis win his 1st MVP?",
        options: ["2019","2020","2018","2021"],
        correct_option: "2019"
    },
    {
        question: "What was Kobe Bryant middle name?",
        options: ["Bean","Michael","Robert","Nathaniel"],
        correct_option: "Bean"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the most points Shaquille ONeal scored in a game?",
        options: ["52","61","55","63"],
        correct_option: "61"
    },
    {
        question: "Who was the number 1 pick in 1984?",
        options: ["Hakeem Olajuwon","Michael Jordan","John Stockton","Charles Barkley"],
        correct_option: "Hakeem Olajuwon"
    },
]